An afternoon with me as a street kid,
or so some people think because I
go out to buy something or pick up an
order.  Being a stay-at-home girl doesn't mean I ca
n't go anywhere.  Of course I
can.  I just have to ask
my parents for permission, let them know where
I am, and come back early.  Today I'm going to
register my cell phone with a
mobile operator, something I should have done a long
time ago.  I wanted my mom to come with me
, since I'm scared of doing
paperwork, but since she couldn't, there was no
other option but to go alone.  When I arrived there was a
queue, but luckily it didn't
take too long.  After I finished
registering my cell phone, I took a walk
around the mall and ended up
buying a small cup and a folder.
I came back and did some shopping.  Bread
for tomorrow, flour for the pancakes
and cheese.  As soon as I got home,
I changed my clothes and gave them their cookies. For
lunch I made some tequeños with
the guantán and the cheese, which we
accompanied with cocoa.  Then I washed the
dishes, brushed my teeth, washed my face, and
did my skin.  They say sleeping with
Korean braids is good for your
hair, so I got them.  Let's see how I
wake up tomorrow.  Bye.